I'm so relieved.
Your spirit isn't broken. You've only
cautiously locked yourself away.
Am I wrong,
Pamela Francis?
Don't you want revenge?
Revenge on the one who did this
to you: Constance Grail?
Constance Grail!
Your Lordship, how is Kimberly?
Safe.
Her arm was injured, but she should
be out of the hospital soon.
Thank goodness!
That ledger allowed us to arrest Simon
Darkian for falsifying official documents.
His wife, Deborah, has been sent
to the Rudolph Convent
on suspicion of human trafficking
and smuggling Jackal's Paradise.
This ought to strip Daeg Gallus
of its biggest backer.
How are you fine ladies today?
Lucia!
You're going out?
Yes! I'm going to buy sweets for Abby,
since she's been so busy!
Now, if you'll excuse me.
I can't believe the Darkians
were a party to smuggling.
Debby didn't used to be like that.
So, did Simon know where
to find Prince Ulysses?
No, and we have mere days
before the Farisian delegation departs.
If we don't locate
the prince before then...
It will mean war?
Do any Daeg Gallus collaborators
control a harbor?
Why a harbor?
The kidnapper is a merchant with
an unusual skin tone by our standards,
yet not a soul has reported seeing him.
So, suppose the prince is someplace
a man like that wouldn't stand out.
That's her idea. Does it help?
Of course! Kiara Grafton.
There's a wharf on her family's lands.
Oh! With the Daeg Gallus tattoo!
She must have warehouses
perfect for hiding a person.
I'll go investigate.
I... I'll go with you!
Abby!
Thank goodness. You're all right?
Why wouldn't I be?
I got a tip.
Deborah Darkian has escaped
from the convent.
A-Are you angry that
I insisted on coming?
No. I was reminding myself
that it's better to keep you in my sights
than to let you run off on your own.
He has a point.
That said,
I may not need to keep an eye
on you much longer.
When we locate Prince Ulysses
and all of this is resolved,
the two of you will have
achieved your goal too.
So...
I don't want to hear this.
So I'll arrange things for you to dissolve
our engagement when the time comes.
Such that no blame falls
on you, of course.
What about Your Lordship?
Won't you marry?
No. I have no faith that
I could make a wife happy.
What a silly man.
You certainly bought a lot, Lady Lucia.
Indeed! I just know Abby will love these!
Come now!
I'll retrieve it at once!
I know you.
Raise your voice and I'll slit her throat.
L-Lady Lucia...
Kindly release that woman, Lady Deborah.
It's me you're after, is it not?
So, this is the warehouse.
It's awfully quiet.
I'll take a peek inside.
Connie.
Oh, right.
Run!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
Connie!
Where are they firing from?!
Over there!
She says there's one on that roof!
Laid an ambush for us, did they?
I saw signs that they moved in a hurry.
They caught wind of us.
I'll draw their attention.
You escape in the meantime.
Scarlett, look after Miss Grail.
What?!
Your Lordship!
Don't lose your head!
What do you think you can do?!
But His Lordship's going to—
What should I do, Scarlett?!
This won't be easy.
Did Miss Grail make it out safely?
It's funny.
Amid all this, I only care
about what happens to her.
Should I risk it?
Scarlett?
I asked you to look after Miss Grail...
Then again, you would never
take orders from anyone.
I see him! He's over here!
You have my thanks.
Honestly, you look pathetic.
Scarlett! You're not hurt, are you?!
Of course not. Who do you
think you're talking to?
Oh, thank goodness!
Your Lordship!
Are you wounded?
I thought I told you to escape.
Oh, Your stupid Lordship!
How could I possibly leave you
in that situation and run away?!
Oh, honestly!
You... Your Stupidship!
"Stupidship"?
That's right! You're
His stupid Lordship! His Stupidship!
Does that bother you?!
What are you laughing for?!
Why...
are you crying?
Because I was scared!
That's why I told you to escape.
No! I was scared because
I thought you might die!
Can't you get that through your head?!
Your Stupidship! You big, dumb oaf!
I...
was scared too.
Scared I might lose you.
I guess we're alike, Connie.
I-If you think a smile is all it takes to
placate me, you couldn't be more wrong.
If allowed...
If I'm allowed,
I would like to walk
through life at your side.
In that case,
I'll allow it.
You have my permission.
No matter who else withholds theirs,
and even if the gods object,
I'll allow you everything.
So Your Lordship has nothing
whatsoever to worry about.
Should anyone insist on finding fault
with you in spite of that,
I'll slap them good and proper.
What man could resist that line?
You say the most outrageous
things sometimes.
I... I know I need to work on that.
Please do.
If you're going to blame someone,
blame Abigail.
Abby's done nothing wrong.
True. That woman is always in the right.
I truly cannot stomach her.
Imagine the look on that hypocrite's face
when I send her your head.
Okay, hold it right there.
Salvador?
I'll thank you not to interfere.
I'd normally be happy to oblige,
but I make it my policy not to kill kids.
So go back to your convent
and keep the Security Force's
eyes on you.
Y-You dare to treat me like...
Oh, but we don't want you
telling any tales.
I'd prefer to rip out
your tongue, but well...
Work her over so she can't talk.
No! No!
Now then, you can run on home.
Help...
You're a sharp one.
They were even serving him meals.
It certainly looks like
they kept Uly alive.
Why don't they kill him, though?
The fact that Uly was abducted in this
country is all Faris needs to start a war.
Theophilis already acts like he's king.
His agents would dispose of Uly at once.
After all, only he and Uly
inherited the bluish-violet eyes
that mark our royalty.
So if Prince Ulysses is being kept alive,
Theophilis isn't the one behind this.
And the only contender who hasn't
renounced his right to the throne is...
Eularia, we're going to see Kendall.
Our enemy isn't Theophilis.
It's Second Prince Roderick.
Where could Lucia have gone?
Abigail's people are searching
and haven't found a clue.
And Deborah turned up
in no condition to talk.
What on earth is going on?
Constance Grail?
It's been too long.
Pamela...
You haven't changed a bit.
What about me? Don't I seem
a little different to you?
To tell the truth,
I spotted you not long ago.
In a warehouse on the Grafton wharf.
I th-think you must be mistaken.
Do you now?
Well, it doesn't really matter.
King Ernst is going to Melvina?
The grenades at the wharf were made
with smuggled explosives from Melvina.
In exchange for overlooking that fact,
he wants a trade agreement on arms
that will act as a check against Faris.
Explosives from Melvina...?
Lily mentioned that in her letter.
I'm having explosives
smuggled in from Melvina.
Crown Princess Cecilia!
What's the meaning of this?!
You never breathed a word
of a pact with Melvina to me!
A strange reaction.
Melvina borders the Luze domain
where you grew up.
And all the agreement will do is
let us trade freely with them.
So, why are you so flustered?
I've waited a long time for this day,
when the explosives you smuggled in
saw use on our soil.
How long have you known?
Why do you think I married you
despite objections from all sides?
Why do you think my father
and Duke Castiel gave their blessings?
From the very beginning?
Is this wise? You could be
accused yourself if word gets out.
Didn't you know?
I've been guilty for a long time now.
I always knew you were careless.
Come quickly! Enrique's having a fit!
You didn't kill him?
He is still a prince. It's easier
for me to act with him alive.
I see.
They've already moved Ulysses
to that dungeon.
Now everything is in place.
Yes, there have been many
unforeseen developments,
but now is our time to strike.
Oh, but first...
we must dispose of nuisances.
Really, it was only by chance!
Extra! Extra!
A prince was kidnapped?!
They say Faris is ready to go to war!
I went to the Grafton domain
on my physician's advice.
And there, I just so happened
to witness a friend of mine
shove a sobbing child into a carriage.
I couldn't put it out of my mind,
so I asked her about it.
But she panicked and told me
I had to be mistaken.
Looking back, I realize...
that must have been Prince Ulysses.
So, that's their game.
Constance Grail, I believe?
I hereby arrest you for aiding and
abetting the abduction of Ulysses Faris.
I've done nothing wrong.
Did Randolph Ulster do the dirty work?
We have testimony
that Ulster drew his gun.
So that's how it's going to be.
Someone must be questioning
His Lordship as we speak.
Time wasted on us delays the search for
Prince Ulysses and moves us closer to war.
Connie?
No. I was a party to the abduction
of Prince Ulysses.
I had backers.
Ruthless criminals who don't hesitate
to kill to get what they want.
You wouldn't!
The name of their organization...
Hey, wait!
is Daeg Gallus.
Connie, you idiot!
Did you get all that?
I have more to confess.
Stop. That's enough.
In that case,
please summon Viscount Hamsworth.
My engagement to Earl Randolph Ulster...
must be broken off.
Your Lordship! So they let you go.
What are you thinking?!
You won't be free to act
unless we sever all ties.
You're going to cast me off?
If the day comes when this is all over
and we can laugh together again,
I'd like to drop in on
a certain someone uninvited.
That someone is strong and kind
and always in the right,
but he's such an oaf that he's convinced
himself he can't make anyone happy.
So, this time, I want to be
the one to take him by the hand.
That will prove difficult.
I'm certain you'll be proposed to first...
by a dull man who can't manage a witty
remark or pick a decent spot for a date.
On my forehead?
I'm not engaged to you at the moment.
Your Royal Highness Prince Johan,
have you reached a decision?
How many times must I tell you?
I'm only standing in for the king.
SECOND PRINCE JOHAN ADELBIDE
Villain! This is my daughter's!
Have no fear. Your precious daughter
has not suffered a scratch...
for the moment.
Faris desires war.
To convince them to
stay their raised fist,
you must make an example
by publicly executing...
the kidnapper, Constance Grail.
FOR THE FUTURE
Translation:
William Varteresian
Subtitle Timing:
Edgar Cruz
Subtitle Editing:
Riley Dalton
Quality Check:
SMR
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan